A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Child Development and Pediatric Care, Accession 2003:046, SG 2 FA779
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Child Development and Pediatric Care, Accession 2003:046, SG 2
1995-2001
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund.
FA779
0.88 Cubic Feet 2 document boxes.
Arrangement
Series 1: Child Development and Pediatric Care.
Scope and Contents
Primarily contains correspondence and grant records.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. Record transfers began in 1986, and accruals continue.
- Commonwealth Fund records, 1995-2001; 2003:046; 0.88 Cubic Feet 2 document boxes.
  - Child Development and Pediatric Care, 1995-2001; 1
    - Kathryn Taafe McLearn Correspondence, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Kathryn Taafe McLearn Correspondence, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - Sports in Schools Foundation (Presidential Discretionary Fund - 96483), 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - National Committee to Prevent Child Abuse-Healthy Families America (Presidential Discretionary Fund - 96698), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Princeton University - Fragile Families (Presidential Discretionary Fund - 970945), 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - American Youth Policy Forum (Presidential Discretionary Fund - 980801), 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Washington Tennis Foundation (Presidential Discretionary Fund - 980802), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Cornell Medical Center - Healthy Steps Infant Behavior Study (Presidential Discretionary Fund - 990148), 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Children's Health Fund (Presidential Discretionary Fund - 990292), 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Committee for Economic Development (990631), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Child Mental Health and Federal Agencies Work (990917), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Alliance to End Childhood Lead Poisoning - Ryan (Presidential Discretionary Fund - 20000717), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Alliance to End Childhood Lead Poisoning - Meeting with Eileen Quinn and Don Ryan (Presidential Discretionary Fund - 20000717), 2001 February 5 (Box 2, Folder 16)